You guys! You must be smiling inside when you are asked these questions!
The Bragging Question Grand Prix!
And that brings us to the last one!
The last one!
The last one is an illustration of the center!
Actually, Aira is pretty really filler and pure.
She's grinning now, and it's easy to see.
She seems to answer a lot of questions that make me happy!
Just right?
I can't lie.
On the contrary, it's just too much.
I have a lot of coke.
You're having a hard time.
Which one is it?
♪ ~ Pretty for you
Pretty for you I'm not going to stop
♪ Pretty for you and I'd like to make it happen
On a grand mind
Tell me now
Thank you for watching!
I've put it all out there compared to various media.
I'm putting it all out there in all kinds of media.
I've been telling everyone what I really am and what I've been up to.
I've told a lot of people in real life.
It's like that. I wish everyone would be taken in.
I hate it the most.
It's the worst.
Stop it, already.
It's free.
Stop it.
You're gonna use my ring?
I'll use my foot.
Use your feet.
I'm curious.
Thank you for watching.
They didn't ask me about this.
I was asked.
After all, this is the most delicious, right?
So, something like, yes, I'm longing for it.
Don't say it out loud.
You've already said it.
Eh, pretty much already know?
Well, but, I don't know... I guess I don't have that image in everyone's mind.
What? You don't have that image?
But, you know, as we work together,
I mean, as we work together, as we talk and stuff,
I think that if you just take that out of it, it might be true.
What?
It might be a little broad.
But, you know, it's Ira,
I think that's what makes me grin the most,
Maybe the one we wrote,
I'm sure there's a question that makes you grin the most that you haven't thought of.
No, there's going to be.
With Ira, I grin at everything, even if I get it wrong.
All the right answers.
Yes, I'll go.
Then please do.
Ayla has a lot of imagination, but if you were to do a live performance, what kind of live performance would you like to do?
I've always said that I want to do something like this or like this,
I think she would like to do a live show where she directs alone,
I think she would be happy if I asked her what kind of live show she would like to do with only Aira's direction, since she has a wide range of imagination and drawings.
I think she would be happy.
You seem happy.
She can't hide it.
I can't hide it.
It shows on her face.
It showed the most.
I'm glad.
What about something like this?
If it's like this, there will be no rewrite.
No rewrites.
I don't see why anyone would rewrite it.
That's just fine.
Next.
Skin.
You have a stoic image. How do you practice at home?
I'm glad, glad.
I knew it. I'm always serious and dedicated.
I'm sure you'll answer me.
You know, I have not only talent, but also ability and hard work.
Thank you very much.
But I don't know,
I think people have an image that you like dancing,
I get that question a lot.
Oh, well.
I'll rewrite it.
Wow.
When do you start rewriting?
I've been rewriting.
It was interesting to rewrite.
Well, if there is a rewrite function, what is it?
I don't use it.
I'm not sure if it's me.
I would accept it.
Yes, well, I found social networking sites,
I thought that idols have good taste,
What brand of clothes do you recommend?
I don't know,
I'm Mr...
Yes, but I don't usually..,
I mean, I don't know,
I'm like, "What's the best part of this outfit for Yuzu or something?
I have an image of you asking a lot of questions.
But I don't know,
When we go on an expedition,
Or when we were in the same room together,
I have the image of them asking me what I want to wear,
or the combination of clothes,
I think about it a lot,
I think she would be happy if I said something to her,
I'm not sure,
I'm not sure, but..,
I'm not sure, but I think it would make you happy to hear it,
I think it would make you happy.
What is your next brand, by the way?
Bauzy.
But lately, I don't know,
I've been speaking a lot of Korean at my core.
Yeah, I know.
You're a cute guy, aren't you?
Korean at the core.
Yes, yes, yes.
Because she's excellent at the core.
I'm glad, glad, glad.
How's that?
But you probably don't have that concept.
No, no, no.
But..,
It's okay.
Leave it to Hana.
Hana's still young.
Huh?
I'm often left to Hana like this.
But..,
Well, well, well.
Let's go have a look.
Okay.
Well, I don't really have an image of you, but do you have a specialty?
Hmm.
No, I don't.
I'm good at cooking.
But, you know, not that kind.
I guess I'm going to start cooking my specialty or Western food.
No, probably.
I make omelets every time.
That's right.
Something like an omelette.
Fried rice.
Omelette.
I definitely like the rush shape of the omelette.
I want you to do it with this text.
Like an omelette.
Because it's not.
When Yuzuki went to stay over, she made me instant noodles.
Stop, stop, stop.
When I went to stay over too, you made me shin ramen.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Then, it's omelette and miso soup.
Stop it, stop it, stop it. So, we have three answers now,
Aya, what do you think?
Actually, there is a triangle. Around here.
Really?
Yes. I have a large area, so there are people who have that kind of contact.
Ah.
So there are people who are narrowing it down.
I'm narrowing it down. That's all there is to it.
Yes.
Here is my coordination.
Ta-da!
You have surprisingly good taste in art.
Ah!
I see.
Is that why you wear yuzu?
Yes, yuzu.
Three yuzu.
I'm sorry, but I've misunderstood you by using the term "artistic sense" to sum it up,
I also like to draw a lot,
Oh.
You were confused?
But I also like to imagine things in my mind and direct them,
I also think about how the candy flash would look good on me,
I'm not good at writing or drawing,
I'm not good at writing brush strokes or drawing people, but I like to use paints to draw backgrounds and so on,
If someone said to me, "Your sense of style is surprisingly good,
I would be very impressed.
I was really confused about Moeka.
I was really confused about the goods.
Because she is good at drawing.
There were goods and stuff.
Then the two of you were a good match.
That's for sure.
What?
No, it's not.
A donkey.
What?
I knew it. You have a good sense of humor,
You're happy.
Yes, it's true.
You're right.
Good taste is good taste.
I'm happy because you have good taste.
You have to take care of your sense.
Yes, I do.
How many times?
I wanted to be imaginative.
It was really easy to understand.
Nothing was easy to understand.
I don't know why we were thinking about it in such detail.
Yeah.
Because we already have a good sense of the general idea.
We should have thought about them.
Like, "You're good.
Yeah.
I should have done it that way.
You want to say I'm an easy girl.
I know.
It's a back ins.
I'll look at it later and see if it's in there,
My mom said, "Aira, I have no taste."
She didn't notice at all and smiled.
She looks like she's about to laugh.
It's not funny anymore.
It's true.
When it comes to drawing, there are better artists out there.
Yes, that's right.
And you're good at it.
It's great.
Really, really good.
I see it.
Tijimabushi.
Hey, guys.
What do you think?
It fits.
It's just Moeka.
She's looking down on me.
Why? Why?
I've been saying it for a while.
It's not like it wasn't here.
Mr. C.
Mr. C's picture is over here.
No, right.
That's right.
It's really not that bad at all.
It's just...
It's good to see them opposite each other.
If you can see it with everyone else,
Anyway,
It shows in the voting results.
I can't help it.
I've done a lot of things.
You know what I just did?
What did you say?
I can see that you are completely throwing money away.
That's why.
When the fans go to the event,
If you are going to do interviews or something,
Not only in real life,
I'll say, "Moeka-san, you have a good sense of ____,
I can say, "You have good taste, Moeka-san,
Anything is fine.
That's right.
Indeed, indeed, indeed, indeed.
Certainly, certainly.
You have a good sense of gag.
Sense of gag.
Yes, he does.
What do you think?
The development is normal.
But the sense of gag is good, isn't it?
I don't know.
I really like all of them.
I like all the gags,
Even the Brazilian one,
I like the sense of gag.
I also like the sense of imagination.
I like the gag,
It's like the quality is very close to the quality.
Ah...
Demon.
Oni.
Like an ogre or something.
No, it's not.
Um, I'm a child now,
You know..,
When I was losing,
I thought, "If I do this, the kids will like it,
I wanted to ask you a question,
I'm already on my way,
You know,
I was hoping for a question that could be used as a quiz or something like that.
I really like it,
I love it.
Yes, I do.
The devil's.
Oni's sense.
I'm glad, I'm glad.
I'm glad.
With this.
I feel like I'm finally saying it.
I am who I am,
I'm an ogre.
Well then,
I'd like to make a gag
I'd like to make a gag that children will enjoy.
I'm going to start.
Oni.
Kari-chan, pony pony pony pony pony!
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Really.
You really have good taste.
That's right.
If you can do this much research.
You have a good sense of research.
It's a lot of work.
Thank you very much.
It's great.
Anyone would love this sponsor.
I love this sponsor.
Thank you very much.